Today, three of us are going out to play.
(A Fun Day of CHINYANGZ)
Custom~
(MC ARNO's schedule briefing)
(Hahaha)
(First Destination: Custom Studio)
I've never done that properly before.
Usually, in my room alone,
(ARNO is used to self-customization)
I cut up clothes with scissors
or draw on my shoes.
Have you tried it, ANXIN?
Yes, I've done that many times.
(Oh~)
I'm actually a designer.
(Actually, he's juggling two jobs)
As for drawing or painting,
I think ARNO Hyung is good at that.
(Even the designer agrees)
That's true.
Let's customize our stuff
and show it to ALLYZ.
Let's have a blast today!
Please look forward to it.
(Planning to have a fulfilling day)
(The teacher's explanation TIME
before starting the work)
I even prepared this (ALD1) logo.
(The teacher prepared a logo title for ALD1)
(XINLONG: Moved)
I've already come up with an idea.
(Hehe)
(Squeezing out paint without hesitation)
Look at ARNO.
He's already chosen his favorite pink,
purple,
and white.
Do we have gray too?
You can make a gray color.
(Black + White)
Or you can use this one, too.
Is this gray?
- Yes. / - Thank you.
(LONGLONG isn't confident about mixing colors)
(Asking for help)
What should I do to write a comment here?
A comment?
Oh, that's pretty clever.
'I'm ALPHA DRIVE ONE ANXIN.'
(An example of a clever comment)
I shouldn't write strange comments, huh?
'The very best!' or something like that is OK.
(An example of a strange comment)
All of you seem to be doing it
without hesitation.
That's right.
Other people usually hesitate a lot.
(Making noodles)
I've done this with my clothes before
but it's first time doing it on my shoes.
Well, as for me,
(//Shy//)
I've done both before.
When I was little, I was bored...
(Haha)
(Kneading)
(Surprised LONG)
(One noodle is missing)
(Found it right away)
(Finally, ANXIN is squeezing out the paint)
Have you decided (what to make)?
Uh...
I'm not sure yet...
(Not fully confident)
(Haha)
I need some inspiration while working on it.
Without inspiration, I can't do this.
Huh?
It feels good, you know?
I got exactly the style I wanted.
ARNO Hyung, what do you think?
Well...
(Taking caffeine for inspiration)
Oh, ARNO Hyung...
That's really~
(Rip-)
(Riiip-)
(Rip!)
(Riip)
You're fast, Hyung.
Oops...
(Crumpled)
(It's not easy)
(Being tough on the shoe)
Anyway, ALLYZ can't copy mine.
It's kinda difficult.
(Of course)
You're good at it, right?
Seems like you're just winging it,
but you're actually killing it.
(Proud)
Oh~ Thank you.
I want to be good at this too!
Hahaha~
(Pride Protector)
You're doing great~!
(STAFF) ANXIN is doing great too.
(Hahaha)
I'm just winging it.
(I'm smiling, but not really smiling)
ANXIN is that kind of guy.
Just...
"Oh, I'm really terrible at this."
But suddenly!!!
(A type with a killer move)
(Already got the knack of it and focused)
OK! I'll peel off the tape now.
(Peel off the glove first)
Once I peel off the tape,
I'll move on to a really important...
Step after that.
That's my shoes'
That's my shoes' SOUL.
(What that 'important step' will be?)
What?
I don't know how to bring my idea to life.
It's kind of...
It's kind of... Street!
(A clear aesthetic)
A street vibe.
You can use this sandpaper, you know?
(Sandpaper?)
To make it like this...
(Shows the sandpaper to help him understand)
Oh, I like that.
(Using sandpaper & scissors)
'I'll move on to a really important step...'
(The scratching sound
echoes through the quiet studio)
What if my socks are showing?
(What should I do?)
(Serious)
If I wore green socks...
(Elevated into a concept)
Or making it show my toes?
(Advice)
Then, turn them into slippers.
Slippers~
(Superior breathability)
Oh, JUNSEO Hyung gave me some socks as a gift.
(Might as well make it look good)
I'll wear the jewel socks that show my toes.
I tried to write a comment here.
"The Coolest"
(Plagiarism risk)
But shoes like that already exist.
I'll go with 'The coolest.'
The coolest sneakers.
By any chance...
Is there anyone here
(First come, first served: 1 spot only)
who wants to go outside with me?
(After XINLONG left)
(Someone who burned out
while customizing his work)
(And someone who's too busy to lift his head)
Can't you get the feel you're going for?
I'm exhausted.
(So tiring)
(A street vibe made on the street)
Is this right?
(Even a fleeting doubt can't stop his hands)
(Moved to a rougher location)
(To pour my soul into it,
I have to do this)
(And the stray cat scratching
continued for quite some time)
(At the same time, inside the studio)
Teacher!
(LONG is back)
(Showing off the footage)
He's really proactive.
You're the first person to go this far.
(Became the first person.)
(Meanwhile, ARNO quietly finished one shoe)
(ANXIN filled his work
with self-love and love for ALD1)
Hahaha~
Guys~
(Still tired)
My work!
My work~
I mixed purple, pink, and black
and made it with color as the main focus.
I finished the first one
and the second one...
(Totally drained)
I couldn't make it the same way.
So I made it with a different concept.
(Revealing the palette)
(Announces the 2nd outing)
Let's go!
(Finishes with a burning ritual)
(This is who I am)
Did you even design this part too?
(This is) A street!
Oh, my shoes... My work.
They got a name today.
Just 'Street.'
(Meaning of the name)
I walk along the street every day.
I dance on the street.
XINLONG ♥ Street
(Laughing on the street)
(Returning)
How do they look?
(I want some compliments)
Did you attach paper and burn it?
Yes.
Amazing~
If I didn't attach paper,
it just turned completely yellow.
So, just a bit...
The soot wouldn't have spread like this.
Not the vibe you wanted?
(Impressed teacher)
Did you try that too?
Nope~
Oh, really?
XINLONG is naturally talented.
Huh?
(Complimenting XINLONG)
I said it to the camera.
Hey, guys~
(XINLONG CAM ON)
I've finished mine too
(Sense of accomplishment)
(Main color)
I made the whole thing black.
The shoelaces are gray!
It's a little different!
Plus, there's a detail
on the surface of the shoelaces.
Like they've been slightly torn
with a knife, you know?
You can see it, right?
Wait, ARNO is back.
(ARNO came back
from shooting the final result)
ARNO's left.
The next thing is...
(ARNO is watching)
I put tape on it
to create a scorched look a bit.
So I did it outside.
(It was done safely)
Wow, it looks super cool on camera, huh?
(Very satisfied)
Wow, it looks really cool on camera.
(ARNO sat down)
ALLYZ!
If you want to try this,
(Like me)
just follow your hunch.
(Positive)
When I started, I didn't expect
that it would turn out like this.
Of course, it's not perfect,
but it turned out better than I expected.
(Might as well try on the work of his life)
Oh ♥ Nice, huh?
It looks great.
(Watching happy XINLONG is hilarious)
Everyone can tell they're XINLONG's shoes.
(High praise)
10 out of 10.
(Touched for the Nth time)
(High-five)
(Even the teacher agrees)
10! It's really 10 points!
Really?!
Yes.
(In a nutshell)
You're pretty creative.
(Looks like it's his lucky day)
(To. ALLYZ)
If you want to copy XINLONG's shoes,
your stamina matters more than drawing skills.
Because they have to keep going back and forth?
That's kinda true.
(ANXIN is in the finishing stage too)
(LONG's Translation Function ON)
What is 'Theme' in Korean?
'Juje.'
The theme is 'LOVE.'
"I am the best!"
I wrote that kind of comment a lot.
I wrote it in Chinese, Korean,
Japanese, and English.
(Self-love written in Nth languages)
And the ALD1 logo on the back.
And here's the key point!
I split Chinese pinyin and used it like this.
'The Coolest Sneakers'
('I'm the best' with 'The coolest sneakers')
I love this so much.
'The Coolest Sneakers'
Wow, it's just perfect.
And a key point is here as well.
ANXIN = X
HE XINLONG = L
ZHANG JIAHAO = H
(Not only self-love but brotherly love
inscribed on the shoes)
Today's number one is ANXIN's shoes!
(A perfect) 100 points!
10,000 points out of 10.
Sigh~
(I created a 10,000-point shoe)
No matter how hard I try,
(Lost by a 9,900-point margin)
I can't beat someone with wits.
(Humble attitude)
It can't be helped, really...
- Hello?
- Talent matters more than effort.
Hello?
(Showing off his talent)
(Shoe customization is over successfully)
We had a blast today.
A new experience.
And all three of us
customized our shoes in our own styles.
ALLYZ, come and try making shoes
that bring out your own style too.
Don't copy us, though (hahah)
(ALLYZ could make them even better)
(Since we're tired)
Let's go eat something delicious.
Are we going to wear these?
Let's wear them.
Okay!
We're walking down the street
after a long time.
(Heading to the next destination)
Yes, it's been a while.
(Confused)
Streetside?
Yes, yes.
- Strolling.
- On the street after a long time...
We're taking a walk.
The weather is really nice today, huh?
Yes, the weather is fine today.
The mood is really nice today too.
Look at this, guys.
(XINLONG's POV)
(Proud)
I'm good at taking photos.
(Raised with care,
ALLYZ only has eyes for things like this)
(Can't overlook the flowers in the mural either)
Hello~
(In Chinese)
Hello
(In Thai)
(In Japanese)
Hello
(Global opening)
Where are we today?
Where are we now?
Where are we now, Members?
In the singing booth.
Finally, We're Here!
It's been a while
since I've been to a singing booth.
Yes, that's true.
This is my first time
visiting a singing booth in Korea.
My first time in Korea!
- I've never been here either.
- First time for all three of us.
(All three are experiencing
Korean singing booth for the first time)
We're finally here.
(Serious)
Let's really enjoy it
(Let's go to sing)
(Today's stage)
I have something I want to check first.
What is it?
- I'm looking forward to it too.
- If any ALD1 songs are here.
(Searching for ALD1 songs)
(Hmm...)
But how?
(After some twists and turns, the search begins)
(Shocked)
Oh, yeah!
(Trying again in Hangul)
(At a singing booth, search
for 'ALPHA DRIVE ONE' in Hangul)
(Thrilled)
Wow...
It's really here.
It's really here, huh?
Let's start right away.
(First time 'Singing My Own Song'
at a singing booth)
(The touching 'Cinnamon Shake')
(Seems to be super happy)
(Making eye contact with the camera)
(The deep resonance of the first song choice)
(XINLONG wants to do better)
No, no, moving on to 'FORMULA?'
(The score revealed)
90 points...?!
(Confidence recharged)
Can you tell it's my voice?
(Do you know who I am?)
(Didn't press the record button)
(Professional spirit)
Oh!
(The No. 1 idol group whom we don't want
to teach how to turn off scoring)
(Next up)
The only song I don't sing on stage
(Knowing ALLYZ well)
but ALLYZ is most looking forward to.
(Hehe)
(The next song is)
EXO Sunbaenim!
(NOW PLAYING - Miracles in December)
(Korean + Chinese version)
(Switching to artist protection mode)
(Switching to the singing booth mode)
(NOW PLAYING - Special Person)
(Audience mode)
(NOW PLAYING - Red Bean)
My mom's favorite song.
(Crisis)
My timing was totally off.
(NOW PLAYING - The Eve)
(I have to dance to this)
(Staggering)
(The body remembers the moves)
(NOW PLAYING - Growl)
(Audience - Choreo - Singing:
The three-person role-sharing system
wraps up the singing booth session)
Hey, lamb skewer~
(Looking at the menu)
(CHINYANGZ's final course - Dinner)
Want some squid too?
Sure.
Dumplings, cold noodles,
stir-fried noodles, egg fried rice.
And there is the pancake too.
Since the pancake is the signature menu here,
let's order one.
(Waiter) We also have mala tang.
(Happy)
Mala tang!
I'll have that.
(Waiter) The portions are huge.
Oh my God~
I love this kind of flavor.
I want to order another egg fried rice.
Sure.
Mala tang.
Chicken wings.
Chicken wings are a must.
What about guobaorou and mapo tofu?
(Guobaorou picked)
What do you want to drink, Hyung?
How about Chinese drink?
Chapai or iced black tea...
Iced black tea.
I've had plenty of Chapai at home.
(Heading to the sauce bar first)
Done.
No way, this song is...
(He seems to know the singer well)
ALPHA DRIVE ONE's 'FREAK ALARM'?
I brought 3 sauces.
First...
Ah... It's a bit hard
to introduce them in Korean.
Anyway...
This one is a little spicy.
This one is just a bit...
Mala!
But it's not that spicy.
And there's a little cumin in it too.
And this one...
(Introducing it earnestly all by himself)
(XINLONG has finished making the sauce too)
(ARNO is almost done as well)
In China, when you eat lamb skewers like this,
you need both... sauces.
In Chinese,
it's called 'ganliao' (spice powder).
This is Chojang sauce.
And this one is similar to Ssamjang.
These two must be eaten together.
Depending on the dish,
you dip them in different sauces.
(Happy)
Oh, XINLONG is back!
What did XINLONG choose?
(Lonely introduction time is over)
Secret sauce!
And this one isn't spicy.
(Revealing the secret spices)
Can I have a bite of yours?
Sure, go ahead.
(ARNO has arrived too)
ARNO Hyung brought a lot, huh?
I brought the side dish
that Chinese people love the most.
Zha cai!
(I love Zha cai)
(ARNO's sauce introduction begins)
I...
I'm not really sure.
(At a loss for how to introduce them)
'I'm not sure~'
The only one I know the name of is this.
'Salt.'
(Hahaha)
For the others, I'll just smell them
and go freestyle.
(XINLONG's sauce)
It's spicy.
Really?
Is it really spicy?
This one?
The sauce I had last time wasn't spicy.
Is it spicy even for you, who loves spicy food?
I ate too much all at once just now.
(Skipping the spicy stuff)
Then I'll bring something else.
Try just a little bit.
Our LONGLONG was surprised,
hurry up and switch the sauce!
Try just a little bit
because you don't know what it's like.
Maybe I felt that way because I ate too much.
(Still, some mild sauces are needed)
(Tasting ARNO's sauce too)
(Finally start grilling the lamb skewers)
Sichuan is really great.
(Start talking about the trip to China
while waiting for the lamb skewers)
(Sichuan)
The atmosphere there...
I've been to Sichuan too.
(A city in Sichuan)
I've been to Chengdu.
My favorite city is Chengdu.
(Guobaorou is served)
I'm going to eat the guobaorou.
(Getting ready to eat right away)
Ah!
It's hot, be careful.
(How to be careful)
(Review of the guobaorou)
Wow...
(ALLYZ, it looks good, huh?)
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please take the first bite
of the third one, ALLYZ.
(XINLONG CAM ON)
(Eat or not)
(Chom-p)
(This flavor is...!!)
(Meaning it's heavenly)
(Immersed in the Guobaorou properly)
(That guobaorou was good)
Mouthwatering Mala Tang is Served Too
(Nom~)
(XINLONG teaches how to wrap
and eat the pancake)
Dip it in the sauce
and wrap it here like this.
(Simply remove the skewer and that's it)
(Add another one dipped in plenty of the sauce)
Like this.
(Per-fect)
Dip this in the sauce too.
(About to take a bite)
(Firmly)
ALLYZ first!
I haven't eaten yet~
(Of course, I was going to give it
to ALLYZ first)
(So, how does it taste?)
(A taste that makes you clutch your head)
(Standing up abruptly)
(The effect of hometown cuisine on ANXIN)
(Handing over the mala tang
he scooped in person)
(The lingering flavor)
Wow, the guobaorou is crazy.
(Eating mala tang together happily)
(Good enough to knock someone out
among the three)
(Revived)
This is how Chinese people traditionally eat it.
(ANXIN went there just now)
Been to heaven.
(Eating whole garlic)
(Eating a piece of lamb skewer)
(Eating like this) Legendary.
I have two things I want to do.
(Discussing themes for original content)
Climbing and shooting.
(Then) Where should we go next?
Somewhere where all the members
can have fun together.
(Fact bombing)
None of the members are athletic, right?
(Variety show mindset)
That's why we can make some funny footage.
If I were to...
(Overreacting)
(Headache)
(Roaring)
Really?
(Tasting the much-talked-about fried rice)
(It tastes like going to heaven on your own)
(They haven't been starving or anything)
(The next target is grilled cheese)
Try it quickly, Hyung.
Cheese~ BBQ.
The other members probably haven't tried it yet.
Or maybe next time,
how about BBQ DRIVE ONE?
Lamb DRIVE ONE.
Beef Bulgogi DRIVE ONE.
Diet DRIVE ONE.
(Rejecting right away)
No way.
Talking is hard right now
because my mouth is occupied.
(It's hard to do both with just one mouth)
(Cutting it up to share easily)
(Sharing delicious things one by one)
(With the other members)
Let's all come here together.
We'll find even more delicious things
(More) and recommend them to the members.
During the fan signing event in Shenzhen,
That legendary beef hot pot.
I want to go eat it together.
(ARNO decides to introduce
a gourmet hot pot restaurant in Shenzhen)
Since I came to Korea
(Except for the schedules)
I've only been in Seoul so far.
- Me too
- I've never been to other regions.
How about you, XINLONG?
I've been to many regions,
but I haven't tried the local dishes there.
So this time, we're going to Busan
and Daegu, right?
(Looking forward to it)
Let's try the local dishes there too.
(Q. Please tell us about your trainee days too)
The life of a trainee...
As a trainee...
(Trying to recall)
Well...
(Takes a long time to think)
Huh⁉
(Seems difficult)
(To help him out)
When did you become a trainee, Hyung?
I first started at a trainee academy in 2018,
and I first came to Korea in 2020.
Did you come alone back then, too?
What did you enjoy most
during your trainee days?
The most fun thing?
Clocking out?
(All agreed)
Since it was a tough time...
(Clocking out was the most fun part
during the tough time)
But you're happy now!
Precisely because it was so hard...
It led to this happy outcome.
(A happy outcome gained through tough times)
Oh~
Nice comment.
September 25th... No.
(XINLONG also has something to share)
(Anyway) After the finals ended,
we all went out for hot pot
with our families, right?
The three of us?
(CHINYANGZ's family gathering)
At that time, our moms
got to know each other too.
(Since that day)
I feel like we've become closer.
It feels like we've become closer.
That's right.
Is that all?
(Furious)
The conversation ended
because you didn't pick up what I was saying.
He's angry. XINLONG's angry.
Sorry.
(Hugging)
(Feeling better with some fruit as a treat)
(Mm♥)
(Self-plane)
(Nom)
(The meal ended with the strawberry dance)
(CHINYANGZ's fun day is over)
We enjoyed it fully!
We had so much fun too!
I was so happy!
But sadly, the other members aren't here.
It's just the three of us.
That's the only thing I'm bummed about.
Even though today was such a happy day,
it's a little disappointing.
(Holding back laughter)
(Haha)
(Hahahaha)
A nice comment!
Okay, this has been!
ALPHA DRIVE ONE.
Bye bye~